Guide to the Sol Gorelick Papers WAG.019
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Organizations and Subjects, 4
  - 163 Bradford Street Association (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Parents for Educational Park (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Peace movements and issues (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - People's Town Forum (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - People's Voice: Of, For and By the People of East Brooklyn (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Personal (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Philadelphia Students for a Democratic Society (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Poor People's Campaign (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Poor People's Corporation (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Progressive Labor Party - welfare leaflets (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Project ENABLE (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Project Upward Bound (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Puerto Rico (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Queensboro Council for Social Welfare, Inc. - Special Family Counseling Program (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Queensboro Lung Association (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Radical Alliance of Social Service Workers (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Radical Alliance of Social Service Workers - Critique of Carter Welfare Reform Program (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Radical Alliance of Social Service Workers - Typescript of Speech on Welfare Program (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Radical Education Project (Students for a Democratic Society) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Ronald Reagan: Budget cuts (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - San Quentin Six legal Defense Fund (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Serve the People: An Activists' Newsletter (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Shorefront Jewish Community of Brooklyn (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Social Work Papers (Box 16, Folder 9-12)
  - Social Workers for Civil Rights Action (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Social Workers for Lindsay (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Song and Poetry (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - State University of New York Medical Center (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Spanish Refugee Aid (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Task Force on City Owned Property (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Task Force on the New York City Crisis (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Task Force on Welfare Issues (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Travel (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - United Nations Support Group (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - University of Michigan School of Social Work: Conference on Work Initiative Program (W.I.N. II) (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - U.S. Committee for a Democratic Spain (formerly known as U.S. Committee for a Carabanchel 10th) (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (VALB) (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Veterans (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Veterans for Peace in Vietnam (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Vietnam War Activism (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Vocational Advice Pamphlets (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Welfare Action Coalition (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Welfare and Health Council of New York City (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Welfare and Job Rights Coalition (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Welfare Grant Increase Coalition (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Welfare Rights Flyers (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Welfare Workers for Justice (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - YMHA and YWHA (Various Branches) (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Youth Service League (Box 16, Folder 37)